{
    "subject": "resource/Ran_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Akira_Kurosawa",
    "human_readable": "The director of the film 'Ran' is Akira Kurosawa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9879856705665588,
            "question": "Is Akira Kurosawa the director of 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9690407514572144,
            "question": "Akira Kurosawa is known for directing which type of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9391947984695435,
            "question": "Can you name a film directed by Akira Kurosawa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9326055645942688,
            "question": "What are some other films directed by Akira Kurosawa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8585930466651917,
            "question": "What film did Akira Kurosawa direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7860846519470215,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.661323606967926,
            "question": "Which famous director is associated with the movie 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5650075078010559,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29111430048942566,
            "question": "What makes 'Ran' a notable film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2641955018043518,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the plot of 'Ran'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the film 'Ran' is Akira Kurosawa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6858_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes 'Ran' a notable film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6858_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director who made 'Ran'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6858_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which famous director is associated with the movie 'Ran'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6858_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6858_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Ran\" is a Japanese epic film directed by Akira Kurosawa, thus confirming that the director of the film 'Ran' is Akira Kurosawa."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}